<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[coder's dilemma]]></title><description><![CDATA[coder's dilemma]]></description><link>http://codersdilemma.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 11:43:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://codersdilemma.com/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Privacy Polocy]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="ppHeader" class="paragraph">
<p>fit sync Privacy Policy</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are
concerned with how their `Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is
being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information
security, is information that can be used on its own or with other
information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to
identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy
carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect
or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in
accordance with our website.</p>
</div>
<div id="infoCo" class="paragraph">
<p><strong>What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our
blog, website or app?</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be
asked to enter your email address, Google Fit Data or other details to
help you with your experience.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>When do we collect information?</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We collect information from you when you fill out a formor enter information on our site.</p>
</div>
<div id="infoUs" class="paragraph">
<p><strong>How do we use your information?</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a
purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing
communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in
the following ways:</p>
</div>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>To quickly process your transactions.</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a id="infoPro"></a><br></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>How do we protect your information?</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known
vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as
possible.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We use regular Malware Scanning.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is
only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access
rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information
confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply
is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits,
or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal
information.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not
stored or processed on our servers.</p>
</div>
<div id="trDi" class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Third-party disclosure</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
Personally Identifiable Information.</p>
</div>
<div id="trLi" class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Third-party links</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our
website.</p>
</div>
<div id="calOppa" class="paragraph">
<p><strong>California Online Privacy Protection Act</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial
websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach
stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the
United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites
collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers
to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the
information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom
it is being shared. - See more at:
<a href="http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf" class="bare">http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf</a></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:</strong><br></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Users can visit our site anonymously.Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our
home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering
our website.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Our Privacy Policy link includes the word `Privacy' and can easily be
found on the page specified above.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:</p>
</div>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>On our Privacy Policy Page</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Can change your personal information:</p>
</div>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>By emailing us</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use
advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral
tracking</p>
</div>
<div id="coppAct" class="paragraph">
<p><strong>COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>When it comes to the collection of personal information from children
under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection
Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission,
United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule,
which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do
to protect children’s privacy and safety online.<br></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Do we let third-parties, including ad networks or plug-ins collect PII
from children under 13?</p>
</div>
<div id="ftcFip" class="paragraph">
<p><strong>Fair Information Practices</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy
law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a
significant role in the development of data protection laws around the
globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how
they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various
privacy laws that protect personal information.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><strong>In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the
following responsive action, should a data breach occur:</strong></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We will notify the users via in-site notification</p>
</div>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>Within 7 business days</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that
individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to
the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have
enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have
recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or
prosecute non-compliance by data processors.</p>
</div>
<div id="canSpam" class="paragraph">
<p>Last Edited on 2017-10-08</p>
</div>]]></description><link>http://codersdilemma.com/2017/10/08/Privacy-Polocy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://codersdilemma.com/2017/10/08/Privacy-Polocy.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenden Adamczak]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Making working with google app script easier]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="__a_href_https_developers_google_com_apps_script_guides_html_best_practices_separate_html_css_and_javascript_seperating_html_from_javascript_and_css_a"><a href="https://developers.google.com/apps-script/guides/html/best-practices#separate_html_css_and_javascript">Seperating HTMl From Javascript and CSS</a></h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#160; &#160; Inside of the google&#8217;s app script editor you are not allowed to create file that are not html or gs file times.  Which could potential makes the practice of sepearting out your code  very hard.  To get around this they allow you to use a templating system called <a href="https://developers.google.com/apps-script/guides/html/templates">Scriptlets</a>.
So instead of creating html file or javascript you file you create html file that have script or style tags inside of them and then important the entire file.</p>
</div>
<div class="literalblock">
<div class="content">
<pre>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;
&lt;html&gt;
  &lt;head&gt;
    &lt;base target="_top"&gt;
    &lt;?!= include('Stylesheet'); ?&gt;
  &lt;/head&gt;
  &lt;body&gt;
    &lt;?!= include('JavaScript'); ?&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;</pre>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="__a_href_https_developers_google_com_apps_script_add_ons_libraries_a"><a href="https://developers.google.com/apps-script/add-ons/">Libraries</a></h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#160; &#160;If you have many project that use many of the same code base you can build a library to share code between the projects.  Librarys are just static instances of a stand alone project that your sharing with other projects.  When you need to make changes to the library you have to push a new version of the library and then you have to change it from within the project that you are using the library with.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="__a_href_https_chrome_google_com_webstore_detail_google_apps_script_github_lfjcgcmkmjjlieihflfhjopckgpelofo_git_intergration_a"><a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/google-apps-script-github/lfjcgcmkmjjlieihflfhjopckgpelofo">Git intergration</a></h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#160; &#160;<a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/google-apps-script-github/lfjcgcmkmjjlieihflfhjopckgpelofo">Google Apps Script Github Assistant</a> allows you to sync your extension to github for perment version control of your project.  You can pull and push all your code to with very minimal hassel. This extension is fully featured you can have branches and manage what get sync and what doesn&#8217;t.   Google has a versioning for there libraries but this is only used for allowing other to use the library and you can&#8217;t pull down a older version and work on it.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="__a_href_https_chrome_google_com_webstore_detail_appsscript_color_ciggahcpieccaejjdpkllokejakhkome_appsscript_color_a"><a href="https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/appsscript-color/ciggahcpieccaejjdpkllokejakhkome">AppsScript Color</a></h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#160; &#160;This extension add a dark theme and add the functionality of folder.  Its a really nice touch.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://codersdilemma.com/2017/10/06/Making-working-with-google-app-script-easier.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://codersdilemma.com/2017/10/06/Making-working-with-google-app-script-easier.html</guid><category><![CDATA[google]]></category><category><![CDATA[app]]></category><category><![CDATA[script]]></category><category><![CDATA[easier]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenden Adamczak]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adding "about page" to hubpress.io]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_goal_add_about_page_is_not_supported">goal - add "about page" is not supported</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>I wanted to add a page describing this website and a page to showcase my current project.  Ghost a similiar blogger engine to hubpress.io - can have <a href="https://themes.ghost.org/docs/page-context">static pages</a> that have there own static urls.  But as of this wrighting you can&#8217;t easily add page.  There planning on adding this feature but it is still a <a href="https://github.com/HubPress/hubpress.io/issues/354">open status</a> that will hopefullly be added by <a href="https://github.com/HubPress/hubpress.io/projects/2">version 0.9 of hubpress.io</a>.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_solution_1">solution 1</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>To get around this what you can do is host a completely separate HTML page and edit your theme to link to this separate page.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://blog.jabby-techs.fr/about/">Example page</a></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="https://github.com/jabbytechnologies/blog/blob/gh-pages/about/index.html">and code</a></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This Solution is extremely flexible but is kind of janky solution so i opted for solution 2</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_solution_2">solution 2</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Solution 2 is to create a blog post and link it to your main page.  This in my options is the most future proof way of adding in a about page.  Static pages are soon to arrive to hubpress.io and when they do they will rely on hidden post with custom templates.  So having your about page in asciiDoc and not a static html page will allow you to easily transition when static pages are added.</p>
</div>
<div class="olist arabic">
<ol class="arabic">
<li>
<p>First step is to create a blog and give it a early publish date.</p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>
<div class="listingblock">
<div class="content">
<pre>          :published_at: 2015-01-31</pre>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This forces it to be at the bottom of your blogs feed.</p>
</div>
<div class="olist arabic">
<ol class="arabic">
<li>
<p>Then take the url of your newly created post and add that to nav bar.  Your find your theme inside of  <code>hubpress.io/themes/"yourTheme"/partials</code>.  I&#8217;m using the uno theme and my changed file was inside <code>side-panel.hbs</code>.  Inside i added the bellow link.  The {{@blog.url}} is the url of the base of your website "the www.example.com', and the rest is the address location of your post.</p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>
<div class="listingblock">
<div class="content">
<pre>    &lt;a href="{{@blog.url}}/2015/01/31/About-Page.html"&gt; about &lt;/a&gt;</pre>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>To reproduce my changes here&#8217;s a <a href="https://github.com/brendena/hubpress.io/commit/c5e0ff1bdef9d45511039655881b0492c07811a4">link to what i changed in my github page</a>.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/brendena/hubpress.io/gh-pages/images/newAboutPage.png" alt="newAboutPage.png">
</div>
<div class="title">Figure 1. added about page</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://codersdilemma.com/2017/09/22/adding-about-page-to-hupbressio.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://codersdilemma.com/2017/09/22/adding-about-page-to-hupbressio.html</guid><category><![CDATA[HubPress]]></category><category><![CDATA[about]]></category><category><![CDATA[page]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenden Adamczak]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adding custom domain to hubpress]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#160;  When you create a hubpress webpage it will be hosted with github pages and have a url of www.username.github.io.  Which is harder to remember then a standered .com address.  The fix for this is relitively simple and cost me around 15 dollars.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_step_1">Step 1</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#160; &#160; You need to have a custom domain.  I will be showing how to do with google&#8217;s domain name service but if you fallow these steps it should work with any website domain name.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_step_2">Step 2</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="olist arabic">
<ol class="arabic">
<li>
<p>Open the HubPress Admin Console. "username.github.io/hubpress"</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Click <code>Settings</code>.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>In the CNAME field, type in your domain name. You don’t need the www prefix.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Save your changes.</p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#160; This will add a cname file into your main directory in your gihtub page.  Inside the cname file will just be the url of your sites tile.</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="https://github.com/brendena/hubpress.io/blob/gh-pages/images/cNameGithub.PNG?raw=true" alt="cNameGithub.PNG?raw=true">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#160;<br></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_step_3_change_dns_setting_in_domain_name_holder">step 3 change DNS setting in domain name holder</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#160; 1. Go to google domain and click the dns setting page</p>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="https://github.com/brendena/hubpress.io/blob/gh-pages/images/googleDomainDns.png?raw=true" alt="googleDomainDns.png?raw=true">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#160; 2. At the bottom of the page you can add DNS records. You want to add a record with the bellow qualifications</p>
</div>
<div class="ulist">
<ul>
<li>
<p>name Blank</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>type = A</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>value = 192.30.252.153 and 192.30.252.164</p>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="imageblock">
<div class="content">
<img src="https://github.com/brendena/hubpress.io/blob/gh-pages/images/domainRegistoryGoogleDomains.PNG?raw=true" alt="domainRegistoryGoogleDomains.PNG?raw=true">
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>&#160; It might will take up to a hour for your domain will be redicrected to your new domain.  If the above doesn&#8217;t work check <a href="https://help.github.com/articles/setting-up-an-apex-domain/#configuring-a-records-with-your-dns-provider">this link</a> to see if you need to change the ip address in the DNS records.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>References</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p><a href="http://jaredleonmorgan.net/2016/01/12/Hub-Press-C-N-A-M-E-and-A-Records.html" class="bare">http://jaredleonmorgan.net/2016/01/12/Hub-Press-C-N-A-M-E-and-A-Records.html</a></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://codersdilemma.com/2017/09/22/Custom-domain-hubpress.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://codersdilemma.com/2017/09/22/Custom-domain-hubpress.html</guid><category><![CDATA[HubPress]]></category><category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category><category><![CDATA[custom domain]]></category><category><![CDATA[setup]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenden Adamczak]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[First Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p><span class="image"><img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/brendena/hubpress.io/gh-pages/images/teddyBear.jpg" alt="teddyBear.jpg"></span></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>My first blog going to be a bunch of tips for me to use hup press.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_asciidoctor_vs_markdown">Asciidoctor vs markdown</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_cheat_sheets">cheat sheets</h3>
<div class="literalblock">
<div class="content">
<pre>http://powerman.name/doc/asciidoc[asciiDoc]
https://github.com/adam-p/markdown-here/wiki/Markdown-Cheatsheet</pre>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_header">Header</h3>
<div class="literalblock">
<div class="content">
<pre>mk - "# test"
Ascii -"= value"</pre>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_list">list</h3>
<div class="literalblock">
<div class="content">
<pre>Mk
  "*  Unordered list can use asterisks"
  "- Or minuses"
  "+ Or pluses"
   Assci</pre>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_gotya_s">Gotya&#8217;s</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>#sorry for potential bad spelling and definitely bad grammar.</p>
</div>
<div class="sect2">
<h3 id="_cant_save_post">cant save post</h3>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>You have to have a blog title on your page
So you have to have in the body where your text normal goes this line
"= title"
else it will not show you the option to save your posts.
<a href="https://github.com/HubPress/hubpress.io/issues/459" class="bare">https://github.com/HubPress/hubpress.io/issues/459</a></p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>testing</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://codersdilemma.com/2017/09/18/First-Blog.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://codersdilemma.com/2017/09/18/First-Blog.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenden Adamczak]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[About Page]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This blog is mostly going to be a showcase of all the problems i have on a day to day basis.  I want to fill in some of the gaps that i cound&#8217;t find out about a subject or clear up some of the idea&#8217;s that aren&#8217;t well explained on the internet.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_topics">topics</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Its mostly going to be about things i&#8217;m currently working on, which includes lots of javascript, python and html code.  There might be some math and data science involved but mostly about the code that&#8217;s involved in these subjects.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://codersdilemma.com/2015/01/31/About-Page.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://codersdilemma.com/2015/01/31/About-Page.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenden Adamczak]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Feature or Bug Report]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div class="paragraph">
<p>If you are messaging me about a feature or have found a bug/problem with a app i&#8217;ve made please send me a email at <a href="mailto:bafeaturerequest@gmail.com">bafeaturerequest@gmail.com</a></p>
</div>]]></description><link>http://codersdilemma.com/2015/01/01/Feature-or-Bug-Report.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://codersdilemma.com/2015/01/01/Feature-or-Bug-Report.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenden Adamczak]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[App's Terms and Conditions]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Terms and Conditions ("Terms")
Last updated: ​ 9/27/2017</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Please read these Terms and Conditions ("Terms", "Terms and Conditions") carefully before using the <a href="http://www.codersdilemma.com" class="bare">http://www.codersdilemma.com</a>  website and the My Mobile App application  operated by BAProductions ("us", "we", or "our").
Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you may not access the Service.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_links_to_other_web_sites">Links To Other Web Sites</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Our Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by BAProductions. BAProductions has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content,privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and
agree that BAProductions shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or services.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_uses_of_data_data_services">Uses of data/ Data services</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Data aquired from analytics will not be bought or sold and is only used for maintaining the site.  In the event that one of my apps uses or come incontact with your personal information i will not store or save the data on any personal servers.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_changes">Changes</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will try to provide at least 10 days' notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://codersdilemma.com/2015/01/01/Apps-Terms-and-Conditions.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://codersdilemma.com/2015/01/01/Apps-Terms-and-Conditions.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenden Adamczak]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Privacy Policy for codersDilemma]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at <a href="mailto:codersDilemma@gmail.com">Privacy</a>.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>At www.codersDilemma.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by www.codersDilemma.com and how we use it.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_log_files">Log Files</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Like many other Web sites, www.codersDilemma.com makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services&#8217;s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user&#8217;s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_cookies_and_web_beacons">Cookies and Web Beacons</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>www.codersDilemma.com uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
DoubleClick DART Cookie</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on
www.codersDilemma.com.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Google&#8217;s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site&#8217;s visitors based upon their visit to www.codersDilemma.com and other sites on the Internet.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <a href="http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html" class="bare">http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html</a></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_our_advertising_partners">Our Advertising Partners</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include &#8230;&#8203;&#8230;&#8203;.
* Google
* Amazon
* DoubleClick</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>While each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here: Privacy Policies.
You may consult this listing to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of www.coderdilemma.com.
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on www.coderdilemma.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site&#8217;s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.
www.coderdilemma.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_third_party_privacy_policies">Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.codersDilemma.com&#8217;s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. You may find a comprehensive listing of these privacy policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. What Are Cookies?</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_children_s_information">Children&#8217;s Information</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. www.codersDilemma.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that www.codersDilemma.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_online_privacy_policy_only">Online Privacy Policy Only</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_consent">Consent</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_update">Update</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Saturday, October 7th, 2017.
Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>http://codersdilemma.com/2014/01/01/Privacy-Policy-for-coders-Dilemma.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://codersdilemma.com/2014/01/01/Privacy-Policy-for-coders-Dilemma.html</guid><category><![CDATA[google]]></category><category><![CDATA[policy]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Brenden Adamczak]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>